Guide to the Walter Lowenfels Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1926-1976; Series II; 52; (92 boxes)
  - My Many Lives, 1950-1968, undated
    - "Jukebox," typescript and photocopy, corrected, undated (Box 77, Folder 1272-1274)
    - "Lillian, My Letter Life," typescript and photocopy, corrected, undated (Box 77, Folder 1275-1278)
    - "Loving You In The Fallout," typescript and photocopy drafts, corrected, undated (Box 78, Folder 1279-1283)
    - "Loving You In The Fallout," typescript and photocopy drafts, corrected, undated (Box 79, Folder 1284-1292)
    - "Loving You In The Fallout," typescript and photocopy drafts, corrected, undated (Box 80, Folder 1293-1296)
    - "My Latest Life," typescript and photocopy drafts, corrected, undated (Box 80, Folder 1297-1299)
    - "My Latest Life," typescript and photocopy drafts, corrected, undated (Box 81, Folder 1300-1304)
    - "My Latest Life," typescript and photocopy drafts, corrected, undated (Box 82, Folder 1305-1307)
    - "Paris Chapters," typescript and photocopy drafts, corrected, undated (Box 82, Folder 1308-1309)
    - "Paris Chapters," typescript and photocopy drafts, corrected, undated (Box 83, Folder 1310-1317)
    - "The Poetry of My Politics," typescript and photocopy drafts, corrected, 1968, undated (Box 84, Folder 1318-1324)
    - Various typescript and photocopy drafts, corrected, undated (Box 84, Folder 1325-1326)
    - Various typescript and photocopy drafts, corrected, undated (Box 85, Folder 1327-1331)
    - Printed material, undated (Box 85, Folder 1332)
  - "New Black Poets," typescript and photocopy, undated (Box 85, Folder 1333)
  - New Jazz Poets, typescript and photocopy, undated (Box 85, Folder 1334-1338)
  - "The New Life," typescript, undated (Box 86, Folder 1339)
  - "New Moon," newspaper clipping, undated (Box 86, Folder 1339a)
  - "New Poets," typescript and photocopy, undated (Box 86, Folder 1340-1341)
  - "No More Guernica," typescript, circa 1937 (Box 86, Folder 1342)
  - "No More Poems," typescript and typescript photocopy, with printed material, 1931, undated (Box 86, Folder 1343-1344)
  - "Notes on Readings," typescript, undated (Box 86, Folder 1344a)
  - Notes and notebooks, typescript and holograph, undated (Box 86, Folder 1345-1351)
  - "Note to a Critic: Artists Are Political," newspaper clipping, 1958 (Box 86, Folder 1352)
  - "Of Olga Cabral's Cities and Deserts," clipping, undated (Box 86, Folder 1353)
  - The Other Side of the Wall, typescript and photocopy drafts, undated (Box 87, Folder 1354-1365)
  - The Other Side of the Wall, typescript and photocopy drafts, undated (Box 88, Folder 1366-1375)
  - "Peace," typescript, corrected, 1960 (Box 89, Folder 1376)
  - "Personal, For Poets Only," typescript, corrected, 1958-1960 (Box 89, Folder 1377)
  - "Petition to the Heads of State from an Unemployed Bill Payer," newspaper clipping, undated (Box 89, Folder 1378)
  - "Playback From Space," typescript and photocopy, undated (Box 89, Folder 1379)
  - The Poem That Can't Be Stopped, typescript and photocopy drafts, with printed material, undated (Box 89, Folder 1380-1386)
  - Poesie et Revolutions, French translation by Francois Hugot, undated
    - Typescript photocopy, undated (Box 90, Folder 1387)
    - Galley proofs, undated
    - Printed material, undated (Box 90, Folder 1388)
  - "A Poet Speaks to the Court," printed material, 1954 (Box 90, Folder 1389)
  - "The Poetry of My Politics," printed material, 1971 (Box 90, Folder 1390)
  - Poets of Today, 1964, undated
    - Source material, undated (Box 90, Folder 1391)
    - Typescript and typescript photocopy, 1964 (Box 90, Folder 1392)
    - Blurbs, undated (Box 90, Folder 1393)
    - Printed material, 1964-1968, undated (Box 90, Folder 1394)
  - "Poet's View of the USSR," newspaper clippping, 1962 (Box 90, Folder 1395)
  - The Portable Walter, undated
    - Preface by Robert Gover, typescript, undated (Box 90, Folder 1396)
    - Drafts and fragments, typescript, undated (Box 90, Folder 1397-1398)
    - Printed material, undated (Box 90, Folder 1399)
  - "Posthumous Poems," typescript drafts, corrected, undated (Box 90, Folder 1400)
  - "Prince Lumamba Speaks," newspaper clipping, undated (Box 90, Folder 1401)
  - "The Prisoners", circa 1954
    - Typescript, corrected, with notes, circa 1954 (Box 91, Folder 1402)
    - Proofs, circa 1954
    - Responses to "The Prisoners", 1954 (Box 91, Folder 1403)
    - Printed material, 1954, undated (Box 91, Folder 1404)
  - "Prosody and Suicide," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 91, Folder 1405)
  - "Racism In Culture," materials for a symposium, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 1406)
  - Reality Prime, typescript and printed material, 1974, undated (Box 91, Folder 1407-1408)
  - "Reminiscences of a Paris Expatriate [Interview with George Wickes]," typescript, 1965-1966 (Box 91, Folder 1409)
  - "Requirements," newspaper clipping, undated (Box 91, Folder 1410)
  - The Revolution is to be Human, typescript drafts and printed material, 1973, undated (Box 91, Folder 1411-1412)
  - "The Rosenberg Song," newspaper clipping, undated (Box 91, Folder 1413)
  - "Salute to John Howard Lawson," printed material, undated (Box 92, Folder 1414)
  - "Second Biography," typecsript draft, with notes, undated (Box 92, Folder 1415-1417)
  - The Secret of Being Alive, 1975, undated
    - Typescript and photocopy drafts, corrected, with notes, 1975, undated (Box 92, Folder 1418-1421)
    - Typescript and photocopy drafts, corrected, with notes, 1975, undated (Box 93, Folder 1422-1427)
    - Typescript photocopy drafts and rejects, undated (Box 93, Folder 1428-1429)
  - "Selby," typescript, undated (Box 94, Folder 1430)
  - "Selected Poems and Communications," typescript drafts, corrected, undated (Box 94, Folder 1431)
  - "Siqueros - 'To Hell With Oxcarts,'" newspaper clipping, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 1432)
  - "Snowy Christmas," newspaper clipping, undated (Box 94, Folder 1433)
  - Some Deaths, typescript and photocopy drafts, corrected, and printed material, circa 1965 (Box 94, Folder 1434-1440)
  - Song of Peace, typescript and photocopy drafts, corrected, and printed material, 1959, undated (Box 95, Folder 1441-1445)
  - "Sonnet: For the Poets of France," typescript drafts, 1953-1955 (Box 95, Folder 1446)
  - Sonnets of Love and Liberty, typescript drafts and printed material, undated (Box 95, Folder 1447-1449)
  - "Steel, 1937," typescript, corrected and printed material, circa 1938 (Box 95, Folder 1450-1451)
  - "A Steelworker Rates the Financial Page," Daily Worker, 1949
  - Submissions, typescript and holograph, corrected, undated (Box 96, Folder 1452-1453)
  - "The Suicide," printed materieal, undated (Box 96, Folder 1454)
  - The Tenderest Lover: The Erotic Poetry of Walt Whitman, undated
    - "The Eternal Meanings," typescript drafts, with corrections, undated (Box 96, Folder 1455-1457)
    - "My Book and I," typescript drafts, with corrections, undated (Box 96, Folder 1458-1460)
    - Typescript drafts and duplicates, with corrections, undated (Box 96, Folder 1461-1466)
    - Typescript drafts and duplicates, with corrections, undated (Box 97, Folder 1467-1476)
    - Printed material, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 1477)
  - "3rd Tarot Book," or "Major Arcana," typescript draft and duplicates, undated (Box 97, Folder 1478)
  - The Thirteenth Lover: a play with music in three acts, typescript drafts, circa 1928 (Box 97, Folder 1479-1480)
  - "Thou Shalt Not Overkill," proofs, with unidentified typescript pages and other printed material, undated (Box 98, Folder 1481-1483)
  - "Thoughts on Walt Whitman's Birthday," newspaper clippings, undated (Box 98, Folder 1484)
  - To an Imaginary Daughter, circa 1964-1970, undated
    - "Father and Daughter," typescript, circa 1970 (Box 98, Folder 1485)
    - "Father and Daughter," working manuscript, typescript photocopy, corrected, undated (Box 98, Folder 1486)
    - "My Last Daughter," working manuscript, typescript photocopy, corrected, undated (Box 98, Folder 1487)
    - "Letters to an Imaginary Daughter," typescript and typescript photocopy, corrected, circa 1964 (Box 98, Folder 1488)
    - Typescript and typescript photocopy drafts and duplicates, corrected, undated (Box 98, Folder 1489-1490)
    - Typescript and typescript photocopy drafts and duplicates, corrected, undated (Box 99, Folder 1491-1500)
    - Typescript and typescript photocopy drafts and duplicates, corrected, undated (Box 100, Folder 1501-1502)
    - Blurbs, undated (Box 100, Folder 1503)
  - "To a Soviet Friend," typescript draft, undated (Box 100, Folder 1504)
  - "To David Alfaro Siqueiros," newspaper clippings, undated (Box 100, Folder 1505)
  - Translations from Scorpius, typescript drafts, with corrections and printed materials, undated (Box 100, Folder 1506-1512)
  - "Travelling Across the Land of Perpetual Spring," newspaper clipping, undated (Box 100, Folder 1513)
  - "Two Women Poets Tell of Peace, Struggles and Hope," The Worker, 1935 (Box 100, Folder 1514)
  - "Un-American," typescript drafts, with corrections, undated (Box 101, Folder 1515)
  - The Unbeat Generation, 1960-1965
    - Typescript drafts, circa 1964 (Box 101, Folder 1516-1517)
    - Typescript and holograph drafts and source material, undated (Box 101, Folder 1518-1520)
    - Poems: discards and duplicates, typescript and holograph, 1960 (Box 101, Folder 1521)
    - Dedication drafts, undated (Box 101, Folder 1522)
    - Preface drafts, undated (Box 101, Folder 1523)
    - Printed material, 1960-1965, undated (Box 101, Folder 1524-1531)
    - Printed material, 1960-1965, undated (Box 102, Folder 1532-1538)
  - "Unfinished Journal", undated (Box 102, Folder 1539)
  - USA with Music, typescript and typescript photocopy drafts, with notes, legal papers, and printed material, 1932, undated (Box 102, Folder 1540-1547)
  - "Verdansky," typescript drafts with corrections, undated (Box 103, Folder 1548-1549)
  - "A Visit With Siqueiros," printed material, undated (Box 103, Folder 1550)
  - Walt Whitman's Civil War, circa 1951-1960, undated
    - Setting typescript, corrected, 1960 (Box 103, Folder 1551-1555)
    - Plate proof, 1960 (Box 104, Folder 1556-1559)
    - Typescript drafts and duplicates, with corrections and notes, circa 1960 (Box 104, Folder 1560-1562)
    - Typescript drafts and duplicates, with corrections and notes, circa 1960 (Box 105, Folder 1563-1570)
    - Typescript drafts and duplicates, with corrections and notes, circa 1960 (Box 106, Folder 1571-1572)
    - Proofs, circa 1960
    - Notes and correspondence, circa 1951-1960 (Box 106, Folder 1573-1576)
    - Printed material, undated (Box 106, Folder 1577-1579)
    - Microfilm (2 reels), circa 1960 (Box 106, Folder 1580)
    - [Folder number not used] (Box 106, Folder 1581)
  - "Wasn't That a Time?," printed version, with correspondence, undated (Box 107, Folder 1582)
  - We Are All Poets, Really, typescript and holograph notes and correspondence, and printed material, 1964-1965 (Box 107, Folder 1583-1584)
  - "The Week," printed material, 1965 (Box 107, Folder 1585)
  - "What Were You Thinking?," typescript, undated (Box 107, Folder 1586)
  - Where Is Vietnam?, typescript drafts and duplicates, and printed material, undated (Box 107, Folder 1587-1590)
  - "The White Poetry Syndicate," typescript and photocopy drafts and duplicates, with notes and correspondence, and printed material, circa 1970 (Box 107, Folder 1591-1593)
  - "The White Poetry Syndicate," typescript and photocopy drafts and duplicates, with notes and correspondence, and printed material, circa 1970 (Box 108, Folder 1594-1598)
  - "White Heaven," typescript, circa 1925 (Box 108, Folder 1599)
  - "Whitman," bibliographies, notes, permissions and correspondence, 1960-1965, undated (Box 108, Folder 1600-1605)
  - "Whitman and the Divine Average," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 108, Folder 1606)
  - "The Whitman Image," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 108, Folder 1607)
  - "Whitman's Own Biographical Note," typescript and typescript photocopy, corrected, with fragments, undated (Box 108, Folder 1608-1609)
  - "Who Died?," typescript, undated (Box 109, Folder 1610)
  - Who Is Lenin? Americans Respond, 1970
    - Typescript and typescript photocopy drafts and duplicates, corrected, circa 1970 (Box 109, Folder 1611-1616)
    - Printed material, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 1617)
  - "Wittgenstein (A Comment on the Tractatus Logico-Philosophicus)" typescript, undated (Box 109, Folder 1618)
  - "Women Out," typescript and photocopy drafts, undated (Box 109, Folder 1619)
  - "Writers Congress Gave Impetus to New Poetry," newspaper clipping, 1941 (Box 109, Folder 1620)
  - "The Writing On the Wall," typescript, undated (Box 110, Folder 1621-1622)
  - "Writings for Worker," typescript, 1940, undated (Box 110, Folder 1623)
  - "Young Black Poets Reveal Bigot White Literary Junta," The Milwaukee Courier, 1970 February 28 (Box 110, Folder 1624)
  - "Zukofsky [?]," typescript drafts and duplicates, undated (Box 110, Folder 1625)
  - Translations by Walter Lowenfels
    - Eulard, Paul. "Peace", undated (Box 110, Folder 1626)
    - Eulard, Paul. "To Friends Whose Demands Are Exacting", undated (Box 110, Folder 1627)
    - Fombona-Pachano, Jacinto. "A Warning for Abraham Lincoln", 1954 (Box 110, Folder 1628)
    - Guillen, Nicholas. "Prologue for an Unfinished Essay", 1957 (Box 110, Folder 1629)
    - Guillevic. "Business", undated (Box 110, Folder 1630)
    - Guillevic. "Tomorrow's Children," music by Pete Seeger, 1964 (Box 110, Folder 1631)
  - Interview transcripts
    - The Anthological Self: A tape recording with Walter Lowenfels, Jack Lindeman, Richard O'Connell. Christiana, Pennsylvania., 1966 August 27 (Box 110, Folder 1632)
    - Conversation with Robert Forrey, 1962 May 10 (Box 110, Folder 1633)
    - Conversation with Ronald Gross, 1968 Feb 25 (Box 110, Folder 1634)
    - Conversation with Walter Lowenfels, Cathy Sampson, Eleana Richards, Roger Morgan, Cindy Rubenfield, and Anne Plunkett. Peekskill, New York., 1970 May 26 (Box 110, Folder 1635)
    - Interview with Arabella Yorke and Walter Lowenfels, 1964 October 25 (Box 110, Folder 1636)
    - Interview with Walter Lowenfels, taped by Francois Hugot, 1960 August 13 (Box 110, Folder 1637)
    - Transcripts of Gaylord Leroy, Joseph North, and Walter Lowenfels, undated (Box 110, Folder 1638)
  - Anthology source materials, undated (Box 111, Folder 1639-1646)
  - Anthology source materials, undated (Box 112, Folder 1647-1659)
  - Anthology source materials, undated (Box 113, Folder 1660-1670)
  - Autobiographical writings and collected correspondence, undated (Box 114, Folder 1671-1680)
  - Autobiographical writings and collected correspondence, undated (Box 115, Folder 1681-1686)
  - Autobiographical writings and collected correspondence, undated (Box 116, Folder 1687-1695)
  - Poems, undated (Box 117, Folder 1696-1703)
  - Poems, undated (Box 118, Folder 1704-1710)
  - Copyright registrations, 1958-1959 (Box 118, Folder 1711)
  - Permissions, 1966-1972 (Box 118, Folder 1712)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 119, Folder 1713-1734)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 120, Folder 1735-1750)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 121, Folder 1751-1767)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 122, Folder 1768-1780)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 123, Folder 1781-1798)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 124, Folder 1799-1823)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 125, Folder 1824-1845)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 126, Folder 1845a-1845v)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 127, Folder 1846-1874)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 128, Folder 1875-1898)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 129, Folder 1899-1916)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 130, Folder 1917-1934)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 131, Folder 1935-1959)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 132, Folder 1960-1978)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 133, Folder 1979-1999)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 134, Folder 2000-2022)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 135, Folder 2023-2041)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 136, Folder 2042-2059)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 137, Folder 2060-2073)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 138, Folder 2074-2089)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 139, Folder 2090-2113)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 140, Folder 2114-2135)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 141, Folder 2136-2154)
  - Unidentified writings and duplicates, undated (Box 142, Folder 2155-2182)
- Writings of Others, 1941-1976; Series III; 6; (14 boxes)
  Writings of Others is organized into two subseries: Writings by Author and Writings by Unknown Authors.
  Writings of Others contains the poems, short stories, essays and plays of other writers in typescript, photocopy, holograph and printed forms. Some items are autographed by the authors. These writings were likely sent to or otherwise collected by Lowenfels as gifts, for criticism, or for submission to publications and anthologies he compiled and edited. Included in this series are drafts of Who Is Lowenfels, an unpublished biography written by Dick Lourie, and essays and translations by Lillian Lowenfels.
  Additional writings of others are enclosures with letters in Series I. Correspondence and in Series II. Writings, as anthology source material.
  - Writings by Author, 1941-1976
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by author's last name.
    - Aaron, David, 1951 June (Box 143, Folder 2183)
    - Abbe, George, undated (Box 143, Folder 2184)
    - Addison, Lloyd, 1965, undated (Box 143, Folder 2185)
    - Adnan, Etel, undated (Box 143, Folder 2186)
    - Ahn-Tho, 1965 (Box 143, Folder 2187)
    - Albertson, William, 1966 June 22 (Box 143, Folder 2188)
    - Aldan, Daisy, 1970, undated (Box 143, Folder 2189)
    - Alhamisi, Ahmed, undated (Box 143, Folder 2190)
    - Allan, Lewis, undated (Box 143, Folder 2191)
    - Anderson, Chester, 1967 (Box 143, Folder 2192)
    - Angelou, Maya, undated (Box 143, Folder 2193)
    - Antara, undated (Box 143, Folder 2194)
    - Appercelle, Andree, undated (Box 143, Folder 2195)
    - Aramburo, Eliseo Quinones, 1965 April (Box 143, Folder 2196)
    - Aroba, undated (Box 143, Folder 2197)
    - Arobateau, Red, 1968, undated (Box 143, Folder 2198)
    - Asselineau, Roger, 1965 July 27 (Box 143, Folder 2199)
    - Atkins, Russell, undated (Box 143, Folder 2200)
    - B___, G___, 1963, 1973, undated (Box 143, Folder 2201)
    - Badanes, Jerry, undated (Box 143, Folder 2202)
    - Baciu, Stefan. "Ukelele", 1972 (Box 143, Folder 2203)
    - Bang Si Nguyen, undated (Box 143, Folder 2204)
    - Baraka, Imamu Amiri and Larry Neal. Black Fire. Galley proofs, circa 1968
    - Barnard, Felicity, undated (Box 143, Folder 2205)
    - Bartlett, Al Sandy, undated (Box 143, Folder 2206)
    - Bartlett, Elizabeth, undated (Box 143, Folder 2207)
    - Bass, George Houston, undated (Box 143, Folder 2208)
    - Beecher, John, undated (Box 143, Folder 2209)
    - Beissel, Henry. Salvador, typescript, 1974 March 14 (Box 143, Folder 2210)
    - Benford, Lawrence, undated (Box 143, Folder 2211)
    - Benkovitz, Miriam, undated (Box 143, Folder 2212)
    - Bergman, Alexander, 1941 June 10 (Box 143, Folder 2213)
    - Berkley, Constance E., undated (Box 143, Folder 2214)
    - Big Eagle, Duane, undated (Box 143, Folder 2215)
    - Bilicke, Tom, undated (Box 143, Folder 2216)
    - Birney, Earle, undated (Box 143, Folder 2217)
    - Bissett, Bill, undated (Box 143, Folder 2218)
    - Blank, Carla Marie, 1966 Jan 31 (Box 144, Folder 2219)
    - Blockcolski, Lew, undated (Box 144, Folder 2220)
    - Bodenheim, Maxwell, undated (Box 144, Folder 2221)
    - Bond, Julian, undated (Box 144, Folder 2222)
    - Boyd, Sue Abbott, undated (Box 144, Folder 2223)
    - Boyle, Kay, 1973 June 17 (Box 144, Folder 2224)
    - Brand, Millen, 1967, undated (Box 144, Folder 2225)
    - Brierre, Jean, undated (Box 144, Folder 2226)
    - Brinkley, Frances T., undated (Box 144, Folder 2227)
    - Britt, Alan, undated (Box 144, Folder 2228)
    - Broadous, Hillery, undated (Box 144, Folder 2229)
    - Brooks, Edwin, 1969-1970, undated (Box 144, Folder 2230-2232)
    - Brooks, Gwendolyn, undated (Box 144, Folder 2233)
    - Brown, Oscar, Jr. The Scab, typescript, undated (Box 144, Folder 2234)
    - Brown, Willie, undated (Box 144, Folder 2235)
    - Bryant, Marcus, undated (Box 144, Folder 2236)
    - Buechel, Paul, undated (Box 144, Folder 2237)
    - Bullins, Ed, undated (Box 144, Folder 2238)
    - Bunny, undated (Box 144, Folder 2239)
    - Burnett, Jettie, undated (Box 144, Folder 2240)
    - Bursk, Christoper, 1968 September 28 (Box 144, Folder 2241)
    - Burton, Jimalee, 1971 (Box 144, Folder 2242)
    - Cabral, Olga, undated (Box 145, Folder 2243)
    - Cantu, Martin, undated (Box 145, Folder 2244)
    - Cardona-Hine, Alvaro, undated (Box 145, Folder 2245)
    - Cardoza y Aragón, Luis, undated (Box 145, Folder 2246)
    - Carrington, Harold. "Untitled Prose Script," typescript and typescript photocopy, undated (Box 145, Folder 2247-2252)
    - Casahonda, Enoch Cancino, undated (Box 145, Folder 2253)
    - Chandler, Len, undated (Box 146, Folder 2254)
    - Chandra, G. S. Sharat. "Bangla(waterpipe)Desh", 1974 June
    - Chantikian, Kosrof, undated (Box 146, Folder 2255)
    - Chester, J., 1969 (Box 146, Folder 2256)
    - Childress, William, 1971, undated (Box 146, Folder 2257)
    - Clark, John Henrick, undated (Box 146, Folder 2258)
    - Clifton, Lucille, undated (Box 146, Folder 2259)
    - Climenhaga, Joel, 1970 April 19 (Box 146, Folder 2260)
    - Cobb, Charlie, undated (Box 146, Folder 2261)
    - Cocteau, Jean, undated (Box 146, Folder 2262)
    - Colligan, Elsa, undated (Box 146, Folder 2263)
    - Colombo, John Robert, 1975, undated (Box 146, Folder 2264)
    - Congdon, Kirby, 1957-1964, undated (Box 146, Folder 2265-2266)
    - Conley, Robert J., undated (Box 146, Folder 2267)
    - Connellan, Leo, undated (Box 146, Folder 2268)
    - Coogan, Garth Penrod, 1963, undated (Box 146, Folder 2269)
    - Cope, David, 1975 (Box 146, Folder 2270)
    - Cornish, Sam, undated (Box 146, Folder 2271)
    - Corrington, John William, undated (Box 146, Folder 2272)
    - Cortez, Carlos, 1963 May 14 (Box 146, Folder 2273)
    - Cortez, Jayne, undated (Box 146, Folder 2274)
    - Costley, William, 1967-1968, undated (Box 146, Folder 2275-2276)
    - Craig, John, undated (Box 146, Folder 2277)
    - Crews, Judson. "This poem is a poem for Dolores Herrera and for you", 1972 April 14 (Box 146, Folder 2278)
    - Cruz, Victor Hernandez, undated (Box 146, Folder 2279)
    - Cuelho, Art, undated (Box 146, Folder 2280)
    - Cunard, Nancy, 1955 April 18 (Box 146, Folder 2281)
    - D___, L___, circa 1962-1964 (Box 146, Folder 2282)
    - Danner, James, undated (Box 146, Folder 2283)
    - Danner, Margaret, 1958, undated (Box 146, Folder 2284)
    - Davidson, Richard, 1968, undated (Box 146, Folder 2285)
    - De Loach, Allen, 1966, undated (Box 146, Folder 2286)
    - Diaz, Leona, 1968, undated (Box 146, Folder 2287)
    - Di Palma, Raymond, 1970, undated (Box 146, Folder 2288)
    - Di Prima, Diane, undated (Box 146, Folder 2289)
    - Dixon, Melvin, 1970-1971, undated (Box 146, Folder 2290)
    - Dobzynski, Charles, undated (Box 147, Folder 2291)
    - Dostic, Gaëtan, 1970 October 24 (Box 147, Folder 2292)
    - Douskey, Franz, 1969 May 26 (Box 147, Folder 2293)
    - Dowden, George, undated (Box 147, Folder 2294)